<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-03-30T15:06:26+00:00</updated><id>https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Marta’s Page</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><author><name>Marta González Padrón</name></author><entry><title type="html">Banana</title><link href="https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/food/posts/2021/03/12/banana.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Banana" /><published>2021-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/food/posts/2021/03/12/banana</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/food/posts/2021/03/12/banana.html">&lt;p&gt;A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds
of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
In some countries, bananas used for cooking may be called “plantains”,
distinguishing them from dessert bananas. The fruit is variable in size, color,
and firmness, but is usually elongated and curved, with soft flesh rich in
starch covered with a rind, which may be green, yellow, red, purple, or brown
when ripe.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>jill</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="fruits" /><summary type="html">A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pizza</title><link href="https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/food/posts/2021/03/12/pizza.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pizza" /><published>2021-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/food/posts/2021/03/12/pizza</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ull-esit-pl-2021.github.io/jekyll-github-pages-y-netlify-itsmartagonzalez/food/posts/2021/03/12/pizza.html">&lt;p&gt;Pizza is a savory dish of Italian origin consisting of a usually round, flattened base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and often various other ingredients (such as anchovies, mushrooms, onions, olives, pineapple, meat, etc.), which is then baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven.&lt;!--more--&gt; A small pizza is sometimes called a pizzetta. A person who makes pizza is known as a pizzaiolo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Italy, pizza served in formal settings, such as at a restaurant, is presented unsliced, and is eaten with the use of a knife and fork. In casual settings, however, it is cut into wedges to be eaten while held in the hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term pizza was first recorded in the 10th century in a Latin manuscript from the Southern Italian town of Gaeta in Lazio, on the border with Campania. Modern pizza was invented in Naples, and the dish and its variants have since become popular in many countries. It has become one of the most popular foods in the world and a common fast food item in Europe and North America, available at pizzerias (restaurants specializing in pizza), restaurants offering Mediterranean cuisine, and via pizza delivery. Many companies sell ready-baked frozen pizzas to be reheated in an ordinary home oven.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Marta</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="junk food" /><summary type="html">Pizza is a savory dish of Italian origin consisting of a usually round, flattened base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and often various other ingredients (such as anchovies, mushrooms, onions, olives, pineapple, meat, etc.), which is then baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven.</summary></entry></feed>